GORAN RADMANOVIC

Senior Front End Developer

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm a web developer, who likes new technologies, challenges and new experience and I'm a quick learner. You can easily find me and contact me through social accounts or on email address. It would be a great honor to work with you.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SENIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER, THE SITE DOCTOR - TSD MAY 2023 – SEP 2024

This was project base job, I was working on the company Shopify application for analyzing Ecommerce data from Shopify web stores, also I was working on E-commerce solutions. Tech. that I was using was Remix Framework, ChartJS, Polaris UI ect..

LEAD FRONT END DEVELOPER, TRIVIAL

APR 2024 - PRESENT

I'm working as lead frontend Vue JS 3 developer and creating from ground up application form fintech industry, with beautiful UI/UX, dashboards and many functionality like automatization of business process and creating invoices.

FRONT END DEVELOPER, FREELANCE

MAR 2024 - APR 2024

Working on various projects in web development fields and building SPA apps with JavaScript, PHP, VueJS and other web tech.

FRONT END DEVELOPER, THE SITE DOCTOR - TSD

DEC 2023 - FEB 2024

This was project base job, I was working on the company web site - application and building SPA app with JavaScript, NuxtJS 3 and other web tech.



CONTACT

goranradmanovic@gmail.com

https://goranradmanovic.github.io/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/goran-radmanovic-70814a9b/

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Faculty of Sciences, BSc University in Banja Luka

COURSES

- Basic Course Of Javascript, ICBL
- Basic Course Of PHP & MySQL, ICBL
- Basic Course Of Java, ICBL
- OOP Course In PHP, INFOARS
- Advanced Course In PHP, INFOARS
- Beginning Course In PHP, INFOARS
- WordPress Course, ICBL
- Team Work Course, ICBL

LANGUAGES

- Serbian / Bosnian / Croatian
- English (C2)

HOBBIES

- Running
- Cycling
- Blood donor

FRONT END DEVELOPER, FREELANCE

MAY 2023 - DEC 2023

Working on various projects in web development fields and building SPA apps with JavaScript, PHP, VueJS and other web tech.

FRONT END DEVELOPER, DIGIMONDO

MAY 2021 - MAY 2023

I was working remotely as frontend developer on the enterprise web application for IoT industry. The Internet of Things is already fundamentally changing our world and our lives.

FRONT END DEVELOPER, EXAMIZ

DEC 2020 - AUG 2021

I'm working remotely as a freelance frontend developer for Examiz company. As a frontend developer I'm working on the enterprise app soluition for HR managers inside big companies. Technology that I'm using are VueJS, JavaScript, HTML & SCSS, GIT, JIRA ect.

WEB DEVELOPER, WEBIMPACTO

JUN 2020 - JUN 2021

I was working remotely as web developer on eCommerce solutions build in PrestaShop platform. Installing and configuring modules, fixing bugs and other things. Technology that I'm using are PHP, Symfony framework, HTML & CSS, JS, GIT ect

WEB DEVELOPER, OOMOVERS

JUL 2019 - JUL 2021

I was working remotely as a full stack web developer for company specialize in moving. My responsibility is to develop, maintain and upgrade company's website. Tech. PHP & Silex framework, JS, HTML & CSS, SCSS, GIT ect.

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER, KOMPITENZ

MARCH 2019 - JUL 2019

I worked as frontend web developer on frontend part of B2B web platform for one of the biggest Germany dairy industry. The web platform was connecting dairy manufacturer and the dairy industry as a buyer. Tech stack that I was using on that project was PHP (Laravel) and the VueJS as a frontend, and also SASS as CSS preprocessor.

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER, REMOTE

NOVEMBER 2018 – MARCH 2019

I worked on various web development project as full stack developer with technology stack mostly of PHP and JavaScript, project are different from classic web apps to moder PWA apps.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER, ALEA CONTROL

APRIL 2016 – NOVEMBER 2018

I worked on the frontend part of the betting and gambling apps for casinos and bookmaker. Also I was in contact with programmers from partner's company and with our clients from casinos and betting house. And one of my responsibility was to develop and maintain company's website. Main technology which I used was JS and AngularJS, HTML & CSS, GIT.

LECTURE AT THE COURSE WEB DEVELOPMENT, BUSINESS GARDEN

JUL 2018 – SEPTEMBER 2018 SEPTEMBER 2017 – NOVEMBER 2017

I worked as a lecturer at the initial course of web development where I taught students to the basics of HTML and CSS technology.

PHP WEB DEVELOPER, BITLAB

OCTOBER 2015 - MARCH 2016

I worked on the web pages and web apps for clients. I also maintained legacy code. In addition, I worked in a team of developers and the main technologies that I used were PHP & Laravel framework, HTML & CSS, and also JavaScript.

INTERN, OGOSENSE

NOVEMBER 2014 - DECEMBER 2014

I have successfully completed the program OGO Sense practices in the field of IT support and maintenance with focus on Client training and communication, Joomla CMS website managment and CentOS administration.

INTERN, E-INFO

SPTEMBER 2014 - NOVEMBER 2014

In this practice, I worked with MSSQL databases, I was introduced to the basics of Delphi programming language and creating a form for entering and collecting data from the database via the Delphi. Also, I was introduced to the design of the database via MSSQL, installing Windows and Linux OS systems and MSSQL Server installation. I also worked in Embarcadero Framework.

CENSUS INSTRUCTOR, CENSUS BIH/RS

OCTOBER 2013 - NOVEMBER 2013

- Managing and leading census team.
- Educating census taker.
- Census field work.

COMMERCIAL MANAGER, PLASTIK D.O.O

APRIL 2007 – SEPTEMBER 2013

- Selling a variety of plastic goods and items.
- Conducted client assessments.
- Supply and delivery of plastic goods.

PROJECTS

https://goranradmanovic.github.io/#projects

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- VueJS
- NuxtJS
- PHP & MySQL
- HTML & CSS
- Shopify
- SASS
- GIT
- PWA
- SPA
- Laravel
- Polaris UI
- Veutify
- Bootstrap
- TailwindCSS
- NodeJS
- Firebase
- PrimeVue